[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What language works in Chrome natively?",
    "options": ["English", "Polish", "JavaScript", "Turkish"],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "prizeFund": 500
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following function of String object returns the character at the specified index?",
    "options": ["charAt()", "charCodeAt()", "concat()", "indexOf()"],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "prizeFund": 1000
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What property is used to change the text color of an element?",
    "options": ["fontcolor", "color", "textcolor", "changecolor"],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "prizeFund": 2000
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "var a = []; What does 'typeof a' return?",
    "options": ["object", "string", "array", "undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "prizeFund": 4000
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which is not a JavaScript data type?",
    "options": ["boolean", "string", "double", "undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "prizeFund": 8000
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which HTML5 element defines navigation links?",
    "options": ["navigation", "links", "a", "nav"],
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "prizeFund": 16000
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What keyword is used to create a JavaScript variable",
    "options": ["variable", "varies", "string", "var"],
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "prizeFund": 32000
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "The # symbol specifies that the selector is?",
    "options": ["class", "tag", "id", "first"],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "prizeFund": 64000
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
    "options": ["script", "javascript", "JS", "link"],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "prizeFund": 125000
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which snippet of CSS is commonly used to center a website horizontally?",
    "options": [
      "site-align: center;",
      "margin: center;",
      "margin: auto 0;",
      "margin: 0 auto;"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "prizeFund": 250000
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which doctype is correct for HTML5?",
    "options": ["!DOCTYPE HTML5", "!DOCTYPE html", "!DOCTYPE", "!DOCTYPE css"],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "prizeFund": 500000
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What value is given for the left margin: margin: 5px 10px 3px 8px;",
    "options": ["5px", "8px", "3px", "10px"],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "prizeFund": 1000000
  }
]
